A Guide to the Katherine Gentry Bushman Papers, 1961-1997
Library of Virginia
- Oversize Maps
  - Historical Map of the Roanoke Valley Historical Society Showing Rockbridge County, Virginia, 1778-1865 (1973)
  - Map of the First Settlements on the Beverley Manor Patent in the Year 1745 Just Prior to the Organization of Augusta County, Virginia (1974)
  - Map of Clay County, Missouri
  - Grants and Patents, Calfpasture Rivers, Augusta County, Virginia
  - Map of Highland County, Made by Thomas Cambelt
  - The Beverley Patent, 1736, including Original Grantees, 1738-1815, in Orange & Augusta Counties, Va. - Compiled and Drawn by J.R. Hildebrand (1954)
  - Map Showing Location of First Settlement in the Shenandoah Valley Known as the Masanutten Grant
  - District of West Augusta, and Original Counties Formed Therefrom, 1776